Guide to the University of Chicago, Yerkes Observatory, Office of the Director Records 1891-1946
University of Chicago Library
- Series II: 1903-1946
  - University of Chicago Photographic Supply Department, 1935 (Box 158, Folder 6)
  - U, 1935, University of Chicago Publicity University of Chicago Purchasing Agent University of Chicago Registrar (Box 158, Folder 7)
  - U-V, 1935, University of Chicago requisitions Van Biesbroeck, George, 13 pages Van Epps, F. M., 2 pages Van Maanen, H., 3 pages Van Rhijn, P. J., 2 pages Vernon, Robert R., 4 pages Victor Adding Machine Company, 3 pages Vorontsov Velyaminov, B., 2 pages (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - X-Z, 1935, Waits, Ruth, 1 page Wallenquist, A., 2 pages Wares, Gordon W., 3 pages Warner, L. V., 2 pages Weinstein, D. H., 2 pages Wight, Elizabeth, 2 pages Wilkens, A., 3 pages Williams, Emma (Vyssotsky), 5 pages Williams, E. G., 4 pages Williams, Robley C., 14 pages H. W. Wilson Company, 2 pages Wilson, O. C., 6 pages Wilson, Raymond H., Jr., 11 pages Woempner, Edward, 1 page World Calendar Association, 2 pages Wright, W. H., 2 pages Wylie, C. C., 12 pages YMCA golf course, 1 page Yates American Machine Company, 1 page Yost, Jacque, 2 pages Young, R. K., 2 pages Young, T. F., 4 pages Zug, R. S., 5 pages Reports on work, 36 pages (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - A, 1936, Applications for positions Astrophysical Journal subscription reports Astrophysical Journal bills (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - A, 1936, Astrophysical Journal Astrophysical Journal, Mary Alexander (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - Astrophysical Journal, reprints, 1936 (Box 159, Folder 5)
  - A, 1936, Acme Aluminum Foundry Company, 1 page Adams, Walter S., 2 pages Adel, Arthur, 1 page Aitken, R., 1 page Albrecht, Sebastian, 2 pages American Airlines, 1 page American Association for the Advancement of Science, 8 pages American Astronomical Society, 6 pages American Men of Science, 4 pages American Philosophical Society, 2 pages Annear, Paul R., 4 pages Archenhold, C., 3 pages Arend, J. P., 5 pages Areson, C. W., 3 pages Asplind, B., 3 pages Astronomical Journal, 1 page Astronomical Society of New Orleans, 1 page Astronomical Society of the Pacific, 4 pages Atkinson, R. d’E., 16 pages Austin Hotel, 1 page (Box 159, Folder 6)
  - Candidates for positions, correspondence with G. A. Bliss, B. J. Bok, S. L. Boothroyd, F. E. Ross, S. Rosseland, H. N. Russell, H. Shapley, 1936 (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - C, 1936, Calbert, Mary R., 2 pages Cambridge Instrument Company, 1 page Camp, E. J., 2 pages Cannon, A. J., 4 pages Carpenter, Edwin F., 2 pages Century of Progress, 2 pages Chandrasekhar, S., 42 pages Chang, Y. C., 5 pages Chant, C. A., 1 page Chicago Astronomical Society, 5 pages Christy, Andrew, 1 page Clark, Charles L., 7 pages Clemco Desk Manufacturing Company, 2 pages Cleminshaw, Clarence H., 7 pages Hotel Cleveland, 1 page Compton, Arthur H., 10 pages Conoco Travel Bureau, 1 page Cooke, F. W., 1 page Crandall Packing Company, 1 page Crow, M. O. L., 2 pages Curtis, H. D., 12 pages (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - D-E, 1936, Davis, Dorothy N. (Lock), 2 pages Dennison, D. M., 6 pages Dershem, Elmer, 4 pages Devany, A., 2 pages Dodson, Helen W., 1 page Doty, R. E., 5 pages Douglass, A. E., 2 pages Hotel Driscoll, 1 page Dufay, Jean, 1 page Dugan, R. S. (American Astronomical Society), 13 pages Duncan, John C., 3 pages Dunham, Theodore, Jr., 3 pages Eastman Kodak Company, 21 pages Ebbighausen, Edwin, 18 pages Eckart, Carl, 7 pages Electronic Laboratories, 2 pages Emanuelli, Pio, 3 pages English-Speaking Union, 2 pages Eureka Vacuum Cleaner Company, 2 pages Evaporated Films Company, 1 page (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - F, 1936, Fensholt, O. B., 3 pages Fisher, Clyde, 2 pages Foote, Harold F., 1 page Fox, Philip, 39 pages Friedmann, Anesta, 5 pages Fritts, A. D., 8 pages Frost, Mrs. E. B., 1 page First National Bank (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - G, 1936, Gaertner Scientific Corporation, 12 pages Gallo, Toaquin (Tacubaya), 1 page Gaposchkin, Cecelia Payne, 2 pages Geneva Lake Home Owners Association, 2 pages G. Gennert Incorporated, 1 page Gibbs, R. C., 3 pages Gingrich, C. H., Popular Astronomy, 24 pages Goldberg, Leo, 2 pages Greenstein, Jesse L., 4 pages Guggenheim Foundation, 4 pages Guthnick, P., 2 pages Grating, 27 pages (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - H, 1936, Hacker, Sidney G., 2 pages Hale, George E., 3 pages Hall, John S., 22 pages Halpin, 1 page Hamburg-American Line, 2 pages Harper and Brothers, 2 pages Harper, W. E., 4 pages Hartmann, Johannes, 1 page Harvard University Tercentenary, 5 pages Hassler, J. O., 2 pages Haverford College Library, 2 pages Heard, J. F., 7 pages Hedengren, Torsten R., 29 pages Henyey, L. G., 5 pages Hetzler, Charles, 3 pages Adam Hilger Limited, 1 page Hogness, T. R., 2 pages Holmes, M. C., 3 pages Hope-Jones, F., 2 pages Hubble, Edwin, 1 page Huff, C. G., 2 pages Huffer, C. M., 2 pages Hynek, J. Allen, 22 pages (Box 160, Folder 6)
  - I-K, 1936, Indian Press Limited, 1 page International Council Scientific Union, 3 pages International Exhibition Photography, 1 page International Astronomical Union, 1 page Janesville Gazette, 1 page Jones, G. H., 1 page John and Ollier Kuiper, G. P., 54 pages (Box 160, Folder 7)
  - K, 1936, Kaufman and Fabry Company, 3 pages Kearney and Trecker Corporation, 2 pages Keenan, Philip C., 20 pages Kent, Norton A., 15 pages Kester, F. E., 4 pages Kinnaird, Richard F., 1 page Kobold, H., 2 pages Kodaikanal Observatory, 2 pages Kohl, Otto, 1 page Krieger, C. J., 31 pages Kuhlborn, H., 7 pages Lee Paper, 30 pages (Box 160, Folder 8)
  - L, 1936, Lectures, 14 pages Laberenne, P., 1 page Lake Geneva Dog Show, 1 page Lake Geneva Yacht Club, 1 page Lavelle Rubber Company, 5 pages Lee, Oliver J., 34 pages Leeds and Northrup Company, 1 page Lemon, Harvey B., 35 pages Leuschner, A. O., 7 pages Max Levy Company, 9 pages Lovejoy, William J., 4 pages Luby, William A., 2 pages Luyten, W. J., 55 pages Lyne, Mrs. Roberta Dillon, 1 page (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - Microphotometer, 1936 (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - M, 1936, McCarthy, O. W., 1 page McGrath, T. O., 1 page McGraw-Hill, 2 pages McKellar, Andrew, 1 page McLaughlin, Dean B., 8 pages McMahan, Paul (Milwaukee Journal), 3 pages McMath, Robert R., 5 pages McMillan Company, 1 page Maninat, A. J., 19 pages Markowitz, William, 10 pages Menzel, Donald H., 23 pages Metal Office Furnite Company, 1 page Mikesell, Alfred H., 5 pages Miller, Allen, 2 pages Miller, Roy, (Postdam), 2 pages Milwaukee Astronomical Society, 2 pages Mineur, Henri, 4 pages Missouri Pacific Lines, 1 page Mitchell, S. A., 5 pages Moffitt, G. W., 2 pages Moore, J. H., 7 pages Morgan, W. W., 6 pages Morris, Charles W., 4 pages Mort, Howard D., 3 pages Moulton, F. R., 4 pages Mulders, G. F. W., 3 pages Mulliken, Robert S., 34 (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - M-N, 1936, Morgan-Struve, 57 pages National Geographic Society, 2 pages National Research Council, 4 pages Nautical Almanac Office, 1 page New York Times (W. Kaempffert), 3 pages New York University, 1 page Norris, William J., 3 pages Northfield News, 4 pages (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - Nova Herculis, 1936 (Box 161, Folder 5)
  - O-P, 1936, Omer, Guy C., Jr., 3 pages Oppenheimer, Harry D., 2 pages Oxford University Press, 1 page Page, Leigh, 4 pages Pannekoek, A., 5 pages Paris Observatory, 2 pages Parker-Holsman, 1 page Pearce, John A., 3 pages Peignot, Ch., 1 page Pennsylvania Railroad, 1 page Peterson, Vivian, 1 page Pettit, E., 3 pages Pierce, T., 1 page Pluvinel, A., 2 pages Pogo, A., 11 pages Polaroid Corporation, 9 pages Popular Mechanics, 1 page Postal Telegraph Company, 1 page Prager, Richard, 1 page Prentice-Hall, 1 page Princeton University Observatory, 1 page Przybylski, A., 2 pages Puig, L., 2 pages (Box 161, Folder 6)
  - Paradox, 1936 (Box 161, Folder 7)
  - Questions answered, 1936 (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - R, 1936, Randers, G., 1 page Recht, A. W., 5 pages Reingold Publishing Corporation, 1 page Remington Rand, 4 pages Ritchey, G. W., 1 page Roberts Everett Association, 1 page Robertson, H. P., 3 pages Robertson, James, 1 page Rosenberg, H., 3 pages Ross, F. E., 19 pages Rosseland, S., 6 pages Royal Astronomical Society, 3 pages Rudnick, Paul, 3 pages Russell, H. N., 3 pages Science Service (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - Shapley, 86 pages, 1936 (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - S, 1936, Saha, M. N., 11 pages Sanborn, H. D., 1 page San Miguel Observatory, 1 page Sayer, Arthur R., 2 pages Schiefer, Herbert F., 9 pages Schlesinger, F., 7 pages G. Schonfeld’s Verlagsbuchhandlung, 1 page Scientia, 3 pages Science, 1 page Scientific American, 2 pages Seares, F. H., 41 pages Seyfert, Cark K., 9 pages Shaw, Robert W., 12 pages Sibley, Ruroy, 1 page Sigma Xi, 2 pages Simon, J. J., 1 page Slipher, V. M., 3 pages Slocum, Lois T., 4 pages Smith College Library, 2 pages Smithsonian, 1 page Sola, J. Comas, 3 pages Julius Springer Verlag, 1 page Stebbins, Joel, 7 pages G. E. Stechert and Company, 1 page Sterne, T. E., 3 pages Stockholm Observatory, 1 page Story, Helen, 2 pages Stratton, F., 4 pages Stromberg Electric Company, 1 page (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - S-U, 1936, Stromgren, B., 40 pages Stromgren, E., 3 pages Strong, John, 15 pages Stroobant, P., 1 page Strull, Charles, 4 pages Svoboda J., 1 page Swings, P., 33 pages Tash Kent Astronomical Observatory, 1 page Tate, J. T., 3 pages Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association, 2 pages Tribune, Chicago, 2 pages Unsold, A., 16 pages United Press, 3 pages United States Post Office, Williams Bay, 4 pages United States Post Office, Chicago, 2 pages United States Naval Observatory, 1 page United States Treasury Department, Customs, 4 pages (Box 162, Folder 5)
  - V-Z, 1936, Van Biesbroeck, G., 2 pages Van Epps, Frank M., 1 page Vernon, Robert R., 4 pages Visitors Walker, Orville D., 1 page Walworth County (zoning), 12 pages Wares, Gordon W., 12 pages Western Union, 2 pages Westgate, Christine, 2 pages Whitney, Edward B. (Mrs.), 3 pages Wilbrandt, R., 1 page Witt, William, 2 pages Woodmanse Manufacturing Company, 1 page Woolley, R. V.D.R., 3 pages Wooten, B. A., 2 pages Wright, Frances W., 1 page Wylie, C. C., 1 page Young, T. F., 3 pages Zabler, Mrs. E., 1 page Zug, R. S., 2 pages (Box 162, Folder 6)
  - U, 1936, University of Chicago Bookstore University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, personnel University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, mail University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, darkrooms University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, telephone cable University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, dome University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, boilers power house University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, roads and sidewalks (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - U, 1936, University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, water University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, wiring (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - U, 1936, University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, accident reports University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, houses (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - U, 1936, University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, bills paid University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, coal University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, light bills (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, orders, 1936 (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - U, 1936, University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, statements University of Chicago Bursar University of Chicago Business Manager (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - University of Chicago Comptroller, 1936 (Box 163, Folder 7)
  - U, 1936, University of Chicago Comptroller, McDonald bills University of Chicago Comptroller, petty cash (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - U, 1936, University of Chicago Comptroller, Yerkes payroll University of Chicago Comptroller, Yerkes petty cash (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - University of Chicago Comptroller, statements, 1936 (Box 164, Folder 3-4)
  - U, 1936, University of Chicago Divisional Office University of Chicago Library University of Chicago Gale (Box 164, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago Milky Way, orders, 1936 (Box 165, Folder 1-2)
  - U, 1936, University of Chicago Fellowship applications University of Chicago University of Chicago bulletins, notices (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - University of Chicago Press, 1936 (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - University of Chicago Photographic Department, 1936 (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago Morgan paper, 1936 (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - U, 1936, University of Chicago Publicity University of Chicago Purchasing Department (Box 165, Folder 7)
  - U, 1936, University of Chicago Registrar University of Chicago requisitions (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago reports, 1936 (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - U, 1936, University of Chicago colloquia University of Chicago student’s work University of Chicago classes University of Chicago reports (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Alexander, Mary, University of Chicago Press, 1937 (Box 166, Folder 4)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Seares, 1937 (Box 166, Folder 5)
  - Astrophysical Journal, reprints, 1937 (Box 166, Folder 6)
  - A, 1937, Astrophysical Journal finances Astrophysical Journal Astrophysical Journal subscription reports (Box 166, Folder 7)
  - A, 1937, Applications for positions Abrams, J. W., 7 pages Adams, Betty, 7 pages Adams, C. A., (Astronomical Society of the Pacific), 4 pages Adams, W. S., 3 pages Adamson, H. C. (The Sky), 2 pages Adel, Arthur (Lowell), 21 pages Agfa Ansco Corporation, 2 pages Aitken, Robert, 1 page Allen, Harold F., 1 page Aller, Lawrence, 5 pages Alter, Dinsmore, 5 pages Aluminum Company of America, 5 pages American Automotive Association, 1 page American Association for the Advancement of Science, 11 pages American Astronomical Society, 23 pages American International Academy, 2 pages American Men of Science, 1 page American Museum of Natural History (R. G. Cox), 4 pages American Philosophical Society, 10 pages Anderson, J. A., 1 page Associated Press, 8 pages d’Azambuja, L., 3 pages (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - B, 1937, Babcock, Harold D., 5 pages Bailey, Dana K., 3 pages Baker, Robert H., 2 pages Baldwin, Ralph H., 2 pages Banachiewicz, T., 1 page Barrett, Storrs B., 4 pages Barritt, M., 2 pages Barth, Johanna A., 2 pages Bartky, Walter, 8 pages Bausch and Lomb, 12 pages Beals, C. S., 3 pages Becker, Friedrich, 1 page Beer, Arthur, 1 page Bennett, A. L., 3 pages Bennett, Dorothy, 1 page Benton, Junior B., 2 pages Bernheimer, W. E., 2 pages Blakslee, G., 2 pages Bobrovnikoff, N. T., 21 pages Bodine Electric Company, 7 pages Bohr, N., 3 pages Bonetti, P. (Scientia), 5 pages Van den Bos, W. H., 4 pages Boss, Benjamin, 5 pages Bourgeois, Paul, 1 page Brandt, LeRoy L., 1 page British Astronomical Association, New South Wales branch, 10 pages ten Bruggereate, P., 1 page Brumbaugh, A. J., 3 pages Bryce, Allan (Photo), 1 page Buttrick, John F., 2 pages (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - C, 1937, Mr. Cable (Wisconsin Telephone Company), 2 pages Calder, William A., 1 page Carpenter, A. H., 1 page Carpenter, E. F., 3 pages Carter Observatory, 7 pages Central Scientific, 5 pages Chicago and Northwestern Railroad, 4 pages Chicago Astronomical Society, 4 pages B. W. Christian and Company, 1 page Christie, William H., 2 pages Societe Chronometrique de France, 1 page Clausing, Leroy M. E., 8 pages Clemco Desk Manufacturing Company, 2 pages Hotel Cleveland, 1 page Cociancich, T. C., 1 page Cohn, Willi M., 22 pages Collins, O. C., 6 pages Columbia University Rutherford Observatory, 5 pages Compton, A. H., 1 page Coolidge, A. S., 1 page Craig, William M., 5 pages Curtis, H. D., 7 pages (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - D-E, 1937, Davis, Dorothy N., 10 pages Dehalu, M., 1 page Dempster, Arthur J., 1 page Devany, Arthur, 4 pages Doty, R. E., 5 pages Douglas, A. V., 3 pages Duncan, John C., 2 pages Dunham, Theodore, 47 pages Eastman Kodak, 37 pages Eckart, Carl, 10 pages Elsasser, W. M., 2 pages Van Epps, F. M., 2 pages Eyster, E. H., 3 pages (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - F, 1937, Faculty Exchange, 1 page Farnsworth, Alice H., 5 pages Fecker, J. W., 6 pages Federer, Charles A., 1 page Fisher, Clyde, 1 page Flammarion, G. Camille, 2 pages Fox, Philip, 11 pages Freundlich, E. F., 1 page Friedmann, Annesta, 2 pages Fritts, A. D., 3 pages First National Bank (Box 167, Folder 5)
  - G, 1937, Gabrovif, G. R., 2 pages Gaertner Scientific Company, 5 pages Gamow, George, 15 pages Payne-Gaposchkin, Cecelia, 10 pages Gaposchkin, Sergei, 8 pages Garrett, W. H., 1 page Gatterer, Alvis, 2 pages Geneva Lake Home Owners Protective Association, 2 pages G. Gennert Incorporated, 1 page Germann, Frank E. E., 1 page Gingrich, C. H., 9 pages Girling, Sidney S., 1 page Gleissberg, Wolfgang, 8 pages Globe-Wernicke, 5 pages Glotz, G. (Institute Poincare), 9 pages Goldberg, Leo, 6 pages Grace Line, 1 page Green, Louis, 4 pages Greenstein, Jesse L., 62 pages Groesbeck, Edward W., 1 page Guthnick, P., 7 pages (Box 167, Folder 6)
  - H, 1937, Haas, Arthur, 2 pages Haas, Johannes, 2 pages Hacker, Sidney G., 6 pages Hall, John S., 7 pages Hamburg-American Line, 2 pages Hamilton Beach Company, 2 pages Harper W. E., 3 pages Harris Foundation Institute, 3 pages Harvard School of Public Health, 2 pages Harvard Tercentenary Conference, 1 page Hassler, J. O., 2 pages Haynych, Basil, 2 pages Heard, John F., 3 pages Hedengren, T. R., 1 page Henyey, L. G., 3 pages Herald and Examiner, Chicago, 2 pages Hertzsprung, Ejnar, 3 pages Herzberg, G., 2 pages Hetzler, Charles, 5 pages Higgs, Charles, 2 pages Adam Hilger Limited, 1 page Hill, Edward L., 15 pages Himmelswelt, 1 page Hoag, J. Barton, 2 pages C. F. Hodgson and Son, 2 pages Holland, Gerald, 1 page Horderis, 1 page Horsch, G. M., 1 page Houghton Mifflin, 1 page Hubble, Edwin, 3 pages Huffer, C. M., 2 pages Hynek, J. A., 21 pages Harvard Summer School, 2 pages (Box 167, Folder 7)
  - I-J, 1937, Indian Press, Limited, 2 pages Ingalls, A. (Scientific America), 1 page Innominates, 4 pages International Astronomical Union, 18 pages James, Hubert M., 7 pages Hennison, E. N. (Warner and Swasey), 2 pages Jahn and Ollier (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - K, 1937, Kaufman and Fabry Company, 2 pages Keenan, P. C., 8 pages Keese, B. W., 2 pages Keiser and Schmidt, 1 page Kent, Norton A., 15 pages deKerolyn M., 2 pages Kienle, Hans, 1 page King, Robert B., 1 page Kneale, Elmer J., 2 pages Koch, F. C., 3 pages Kodaikanal Observatory, 2 pages Kohl, Otto, 1 page Kopff, A., 3 pages Kreiken, E. A., 7 pages Krieger, C. J., 54 pages Kuiper, G. P., 23 pages Kunstmann, John G., 5 pages (Box 168, Folder 2)
  - L, 1937, Land, W. G. (Harvard Tercentenary), 3 pages Laves, Jurt, 2 pages Lee, Oliver J., 7 pages Lemon, H. B., 1 page Leuschner, A. O., 3 pages Life magazine, 1 page Linke, W., 1 page London Mathematical Society, 1 page Luby, William A., 2 pages Lundmark, K., 3 pages Luyten, W. J., 35 pages (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - M, 1937, McCarthy, Edward L., 2 pages McGraw-Hill, 1 page McLaughlin, Dean B., 9 pages McMath, Robert R., 10 pages McVittie, G. C., 6 pages Maninat, A. J. Saldiasy, 5 pages Marchant Calculating Machine Company, 4 pages Markowitz, William, 4 pages Marshall, Roy K., 2 pages Martian Observatory, Decorah, Iowa, 2 pages Martz, E. P., Jr., 3 pages Mellish, John E., 1 page Menzel, Donald H., 20 pages Micro Switch Corporation, 7 pages Miller, Freeman D., 7 pages Millikin, Robert A., 2 pages Milwaukee Alumni Club, 1 page Milwaukee Astronomical Society, 5 pages Milwaukee Journal, 1 page Mines, Louis, 5 pages Mineur, H., 8 pages Minnaert, M., 20 pages Mitchell, S. A., 1 page Moffitt, G. W., 6 pages Monk, George S., 3 pages Monroe Company, 3 pages Moore, Charlotte E., 3 pages Morison, G. A., 1 page Morrell, J. C., 4 pages Moulds, John F., 1 page Moulton, F. R., 7 pages Muller, Rolf, 2 pages Mulliken, Robert S., 10 pages (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - Monograph, cost of printing, 1937 (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - Monograph, Bok, 1937 (Box 168, Folder 6)
  - N-P, 1937, Nassau, J. J., 7 pages National Academy of Sciences, 61 pages National Broadcasting Company, 1 page National Research Council, 1 page National Geographic Society, 2 pages Nautical Almanac Office, 1 page New York Public Library, 2 pages New York Times, 1 page Neymann, 2 pages Nicolaides, N., 2 pages Nielson, J. Rud, 2 pages Northfield News, 2 pages Oleson, Loyd C., 2 pages O’Keffe, John A., 2 pages Olivier, Charles P., 1 page Oort, J. H., 6 pages Oxford University Press, 3 pages Patrick, J. E., 1 page Pearce, John A., 1 page Pearson, Fred, 3 pages Peters, Paul E., 3 pages Petersen, William F., 8 pages Petrie, R. M., 8 pages Pettit, Edison, 3 pages Photographic Society of America, 1 page International Salon of Photography, 2 pages Plakidis, S., 4 pages Plaskett, J. S., 5 pages Pogo, Alexander, 4 pages Polaroid Corporation, 1 page Porter, Russell, 1 page Postal Telegraph Company Kenosha, 1 page Prager, Richard, 1 page Precision Thermometer, 2 pages Prentice-Hall, 2 pages Stevens-Prokopoff, Stephen G., 2 pages Putilin, I. I., 2 pages (Box 168, Folder 7)
  - P-Q, 1937, Paradox Quantrell, 1 page Questions (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - R, 1937, Radcliffe Observatory, 1 page Reber, Grote, 4 pages Remington Rand, 2 pages Robertson, H. P., 8 pages Rogers, F. T. Jr., 2 pages Rosenberg, Hans O., 17 pages Ross, Frank E., 17 pages Royal Observatory, Greenwich, 2 pages Royal Soc. Sciences, Liege, 1 page Rudnick, Jessie, 5 pages Rudnick, Paul, 3 pages Russell, Henry N., 36 pages Rust, C. F., 3 pages Reprints (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - S, 1937, Science Service, 5 pages Shapley, 65 pages Struve, 28 pages (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - S, 1937, Saha, M. N., 1 page Sawyer, Ralph A., 4 pages Schlesinger, Frank, 19 pages Schneller, H., 2 pages Schoenberg, E., 10 pages Science, 2 pages Scientia, 2 pages Scientific American, 3 pages Scientific Monthly, 2 pages Scott, Almere, 2 pages Library International Seeber, 2 pages Sen, N. R., 3 pages Seyfert, Carl, 2 pages Shaw, R. William, 2 pages Sherman, Frances, 12 pages Shortley, George H., 2 pages Sibley, RuRoy, 6 pages Sigma Xi, 6 pages Slipher, V. M., 1 page Smart, W. M., 1 page Smiley, Charles H., 16 pages Smithsonian Institute, 1 page Snyder, Franklyn, 4 pages Spitzer, Lyman, Jr., 6 pages Julius Springer Verlag, 1 page Stearns, C. L., 2 pages Stebbins, Joel, 5 pages G. E. Stechert and Company, 1 page Alfred Sterges, 1 page Sterne, T. E., 4 pages Stetson, H. T., 2 pages Stevens, Blamey, 6 pages Stewart, O. J., 2 pages Stratton, F., 22 pages Stromgren, B., 17 pages Stromgren, Elis, 13 pages Swings, P., 34 pages (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - T-V, 1937, Thackeray, A. D., 2 pages Thompson, Clem O., 2 pages Tiholz, John, 1 page Ufford, C. W., 2 pages Unsold, A., 10 pages United States Post Office, 5 pages United States Treasury Department, Customs, 2 pages United States Weather Bureau, 6 pages University Extension, 1 page Van Biesbroeck, G., 1 page V. D. Pahlen, V., 1 page Veselik, V., 1 page Vishnevsky, M. N., 5 pages Volochine, F. E., 1 page Vyssotsky, A. N., 2 pages Visitors (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - W-Z, 1937, Wagman, Nicholas E., 2 pages Wares, Gordon, 8 pages Watson, Fletcher, 4 pages Western Union, 4 pages Wight, Elizabeth, 3 pages Wildt, Rupert, 9 pages Williams, Robley C., 6 pages Wilson, Edwin B., 1 page Wooley, R. V. D. R., 3 pages Wurm, K., 13 pages W. M. Welch Manufacturing Company, 1 page Westgate, Christine, 2 pages Westrom, V., 1 page George Williams College, 3 pages Wilson, Emily N., 2 pages Wilson, Raymond H., Jr., 3 pages Winans, J. G., 3 pages Wisconsin Telephone Company, 1 page World Congress of Universal Documentation, 1 page Zwicky, F., 9 pages Zerfoss, K. P., 6 pages Young, T. F., 2 pages Zabler, E. W., 2 pages Carl Zeiss, Incorporated, 2 pages (Box 169, Folder 6)
  - U, 1937, University of Chicago Bookstore University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - U, 1937, University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, houses (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - U, 1937, University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, accident reports University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, bills paid University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, coal (Box 170, Folder 3)